Guide to the School of Business and Public Management records, 1925-2004 RG0013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Videotapes, 1988-1998; RG0013 Series 12; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains thirty-one vhs video tapes. The material covers the years 1988-98. Subjects of these tapes include Ben Bradlee, J.W. Marriott, George Schultz, Ted Turner, Caspar Weinberger, Mort Zuckerman, the International CEO of the Year Award, and President Trachtenberg. It was formerly Acc. #1071.
  - Akers, John (IBM) - CEO of the Year, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bainum, Stewart (Manor Care) - CEO of the Year, 04/28/1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bennett, Jr., W. Tapley - speech to School of Business, 10/23/1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bradlee, Ben - speech to School of Business, 01/23/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bright, Stanley - Alumnus of the Year, 05/03/1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Friedman, Emanuel (FBR) - CEO of the Year, 04/30/1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fuerstein, Aaron (Malden Mills) - CEO of the Year, 04/30/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gordon, Ellen (Tootsie Roll) - CEO of the Year, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hancock, Jack - Alumnus of the Year, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hunter, Philip - School of Business Alumni Luncheon, 05/06/1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - International CEO of the Year, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - International CEO of the Year, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - International CEO of the Year, 02/1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, James (Fannie Mae) - CEO of the Year, 03/09/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kiplinger, Knight (Kiplinger Financial) - Alumni Luncheon, 12/07/1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kuwait Hostage group - message to IMAD, GW, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Delano - Social Responsibility Award, 12/27/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Marriot, J.W. (Marriott) - speech to School of Business, 03/05/1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Murray, Allen (Mobil Corporation) - CEO of the Year, 03/20/1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Regardie, Bill (Regardie's) - School of Business Luncheon, 05/18/1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rogers, Jr., C.B. "Jack" - speech to School of Business, 05/08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Shalikashvili, General - Alumni Award, 03/03/1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Shultz, George - Statesman of the Year, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Spero, Joan Edelman - Statesperson of the Year, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Winners Circle - School of Government & Business Administration; date unknown, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel - School of Business Alumni Luncheon, 02/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Turner, Ted (Turner Broadcasting)- CEO of the Year, 03/16/1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Weinberger, Caspar - Statesman of the Year, 02/20/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Zuckerman, Mortimer (US News & World Report)) - Alumni Luncheon, 03/04/1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GW History project (rough cut), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Promotional tape "The George Washington University,", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Publications, 1995-2000; RG0013 Series 13; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains publications. These publications date from 1995-2000. The publication "GW Business" began as "Perspectives" and then became "Centerpiece".
  - "GW Business" -- Publication of the School of Business and Public Management (began as "Perspectives" and became "Centerpiece"), 1995-2000
- "Policy Perspectives", 1994-1999, 2001, 2009-2013; RG0013 Series 14; 1 Linear Feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series contains the journal "Policy Perspectives." These issues date from 1994-99, 2001, and 2008-2013.
  - Policy Perspectives, 1994-1999 (Box 1)
  - Economic Growth and the State of Humanity, April 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2008; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2009; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2010; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2011; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2012; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Policy Perspectives, Spring 2013; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "Washington Edition", 1986-1996; RG0013 Series 15; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains the newsletter "Washington Edition." The issues date form 1986-96. This newsletter is a publication of the Alumni Association.
  - (Spring) 1986, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - (Spring and Fall) 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - (Spring) 1989, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - (Spring and Fall) 1990, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - (Spring and Fall) 1991, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - (Spring and Fall) 1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - (Fall) 1993, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - (Fall) 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - (Fall/Winter) 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Tuesday Report", 1981-1990; RG0013 Series 16; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains the newsletter "Tuesday Report." The issues run from 1981-90.
  - Nos. 1-6, 09/01/1981-11/17/1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nos. 7-21, 01/26/1982-12/07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nos. 22-26, 01/18/1983-12/20/1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nos. 37-52, 01/17/1984-12/18/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nos. 53-68, 01/15/1985-12/17/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 69-82, 01/14/1986-12/09/1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nos. 83-97, 01/13/1987-12/15/1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nos. 98-112 (missing 110), 02/02/1988-12/13/1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nos. 113-122 (missing 115), 01/10/1989-12/12/1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Nos. 123-131 (missing 125 & 128), 01/16/1990-11/20/1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Business Administration Department, 1982-1986; RG0013 Series 17; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains course descriptions and syllabi from 1982-86.
  - Syllabus: BAd 341-10, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Syllabus: BAd 253-10, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Report Writing Potholes, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Syllabus: BAd 341-10, Session 1&2, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Syllabus: BAd 341-10, Session 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bad 341-10: Copies of Overheads, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Business Administration program [1/2], 1987-1989; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Business Administration program [2/2], 1987-1989; Series 17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Ben Burdetsky file, undated; RG0013 Series 18; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains obituaries, personal data sheets, negatives and photographs of Ben Burdetsky the former dean of the school.
  Formerly ACC#827
  - Howard, Wallace F.: Nuclear Proliferation- Prospects and Policies, 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Robert T.: Comparison of the Forest Services of the United States and Sweden, 04/28/1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Verdun, Harold C.: A Comparative Study of Canadian and United States Government Insurance Programs, 05/10/1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Olsson, Ward T.: Management of the Military Space Program in the Department of the Air Force, 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Larson, Albert G.: Integrated Logistics Support for Navy Weapon Systems and Equipment; An Evaluation, 06/1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hardy, Alan H. An Analysis of the Organizational and Functional Relationships of Air Force Base and Depot Level Maintenance, 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Wyvill, Thomas A. A Study of the American Lottery in the Past and Present, With An Outlook for the Future, 01/04/1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pegler, Dewey S.: The Role of Military Mapping, Charting and Geodesy In International Economic Development Programs, 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ryland, Russell S.: Assisting the Junior Officer in Career Success -- Thesis not accepted for M.P.A., 06/1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Departmental files, 1925-2011; RG0013 Series 20; 3 Linear Feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes newspaper clippings, bulletins, correspondence, publications, They range in date from 1925 to 2004. They concern the National League of Masonic clubs, scholarships, the School of Foreign Service, the School of Government, the School of Government and Business Administration, the masonic club, George Washington's gavel, fundraising for a new building, the Scottish Rite News Bureau, the publication "The Kraftsman", seminars, and conferences.
  - Alumni - Alumni Association - School of Government and Business Administration - Alumni Associations, 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni - Alumni Association - School of Business and Public Management, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Business - Business Affairs office, 08/21/1970-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - brochures, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - conferences, special events, etc., 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Department of Urban Planning and Real Estate Development, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Faculty, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Fellowships - Scottish Rite, 1964-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Business and Public Management, School of (1990-), 1990-2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Business and Public Management, School of (1990-) - annual reports, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - graduate programs [1/2], 1990 -- --ca. --2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - graduate programs [2/2], 1990 -- --ca. --2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - History - Culture of Change booklet, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Ph.D. program, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - student handbooks, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Support Material to the Self-Evaluation Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Business and Public Management, School of - Wolcott Foundation scholars, 1963-1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Government and Business Administration, School of - seminars, institutes, etc. - publications, 10/13/1981-04/08/1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960), 1925-1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960) - Foreign Affairs program, 1925-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960) - graduate programs, 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960) - programs, 1934-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960) - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Government, School of (1928-1960) - seminars, institutes, conferences, workshops, etc., 1936-1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of, 1982-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - admissions, 1967-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Advanced Management Education Center - seminars, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - doctoral programs, 1951-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - doctoral programs - handbooks, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - faculty, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - faculty handbooks, 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - faculty handbooks, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - graduate admissions, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - graduate programs, 1959-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - health care & administration, 1974-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - health care & administration - brochures, 1959-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Management Science, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - National Association of Schools of Public Affairs and Administration (NASPAA) Self-Study Report, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Navy Graduate Comptrollership Program - Theses, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Navy Graduate Financial Management Program, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Navy Graduate Financial Management Program - Theses, 1952-1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - off campus graduade programs, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - programs, 1967-1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Public Administration program, 1962-1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - Public Administration program - student papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - scholarships & fellowships, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - SGBA research, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of - seminars, institutes, etc., 1968-1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Masonic involvement with the University, 06/30/1925-2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Directory, 1986-1987; 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Degree Program Materials, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The School of Public Policy and Public Administration Program Information, 2000-2012; Series 20 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Elliott School of International Affairs Materials, 2004-2011; Series 20 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - School of Government, Business, and International Affairs promotional materials, 1962; Series 20 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Culture of change, 2003; Series 20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - School of Business Promotional Materials, 2006; Series 20 (Box 3, Folder 7)